[Music]
so what you need about quality and field
control exactly the sourcing of our
ingredients and quality control sourcing
of our ingredients is unique there may
be a couple companies are really do a
good job on sourcing where is the topic
I would say is properly the amount of
ingredients the number of pathways that
are effective and the actual total
milligrams of each ingredient why
there's a lot of capsules that are
involved in pairs a most entropic stacks
all of these are differentiators that
the real differentiator is systems
design comprehend unity both in terms of
how many pathways are affected
how many aspects of each Hathway are
effective the redundancy and how we
affect those and how many cognitive
abilities and psychological states are
being affected and you want to switch
those things all being introspective
desiring sucess there are a bunch of
very interesting chemicals that on their
own affect specific cognitive
capabilities or states that are
meaningful but they're only a part of
what people are really typically on the
fly so you can look at a particular
controlling PR ld50 threes ability to
increase digit span will increase digits
being able to hold more digits more
memory school and for a few professions
that spur to getting equal by itself but
for most people that's only interested
in conjunction with the sustained
attention and focus that allow them to
actually apply that and not be stuck in
procrastination not even thinking about
whatever it is all numbers many people
get any combination of that with their
speed of memory so how quickly they can
retrieve things not just digit and but
verbal fluency
I mean it's addition there are many
things that come together to make up
meaningful cost okay
and analytic capabilities and
competitiveness here very different we
want to increase our ability to have
detailed analysis and critical thinking
or you want to increase our ability for
pattern recognition and create an IQ
both the states who are interested in
involved both of these and this is
another big part of the differentiator
in in our design process of quality is
that rather than having trade-offs and
what's assumed to be a zero-sum capacity
system to increase something is the
increasing real system our goal is how
do we actually to miss with a where the
system is more efficient overall and how
do we actually increase the net capacity
and that information processing back to
the system so it can be simultaneously
more driven and one present at the same
time you can have more deep focus and
better task coaching at the same time
these are typically things that are in
dialectics that have traded off one for
the other that the quote matter and so
our goal is are we simultaneously
Optimates across meaningful things that
are usually dielectric by increasing
system efficiency and total system
capacity and this is why so much of the
formulas not only focused on real time
chemistry but is focused on things like
neurogenesis and synaptogenesis and
synaptic plasticity which is how we
actually support the development in
endogenous process development of neural
stem cell production and differentiation
and long term potentiation plasticity so
that you can actually be involving a
more complex information processing
system that has more net
[Music]